limewire.org 2011-12-02

# Privacy Policy | OfficeDrop

## Last modified: February 15, 2010

Click here to know more about security.

We recognize that your privacy is critical, especially given that we aggregate your personal and protected information. We will do everything we can to protect your privacy and preserve your trust.

OfficeDrop is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site http://www.pixily.com and http://www.officedrop.com. Because OfficeDrop wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Anand Rajaram at anandrajaram@officedrop.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

## What we collect:

  * Information you provide: When you sign up for a OfficeDrop Account promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). We use this information only to provide you the service that we offer and do not use such personally identifiable information it for other purposes. If you are a guest user accessing OfficeDrop without a OfficeDrop account (such as viewing a document that a OfficeDrop user shared with you), we use your email address for authentication purposes only. 
  * Cookies: We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 
    * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status. 
    * Our cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
    * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services.
  * Logs: Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser 
  * User communications: When you send email or other communication to OfficeDrop, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 
  * Newsletters: You may choose to modify your email notification preferences by clicking on the “Preferences” link in your Account page (which can accessed by clicking the under the “account” link in the navigation bar).   
Any passive information collected (for example via cookies) is not linked back to personally identifiable information, and is only used at an aggregated level. We may contact you based on information identified from our logs, but this will only be for providing information we feel that you need to be aware of (such as system level errors that you may not have noticed in the application etc,.) 

## Sharing with third parties

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share your personal information with:

  * Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as web analytics, online customer service, fraud investigations, bill collection, credit card processors, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards).
  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service). 
  * Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation, court order, subpoena, warrant or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation.
  * Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.)

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

## No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing

We do not tolerate spam. You may not use our communication tools (such as sharing documents) to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We may automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content, but we do not permanently store messages sent through these tools. If you send an email through OfficeDrop (for example, while sharing documents), we do store that email to show you who you have sent the message to. We will not use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses.

## Blog

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

## Invite Friends

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. OfficeDrop stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email [and tracking the success of our referral program]. Your friend may contact us at support@officedrop.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

## Account Protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your OfficeDrop password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify OfficeDrop and change your password.

## Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to OfficeDrop. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce the OfficeDrop User Agreement and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

## Online Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. (10a, 10b) All the communication between your browser and our servers is encrypted using 128-bit SSL encryption so that no one else will be able intercept the communication. We also run hacker-safe tests daily to ensure that our servers are completely hacker-proof. Personal information is known only by employees with a need-to-know (such as Customer Service personnel). However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

## Physical Security

All the scanning happens in the United States. All personnel authorized for scanning go through background checks. Under normal load circumstances, OfficeDrop will digitize and upload the documents we receive within two working days. OfficeDrop does not guarantee this turnaround time as our load may vary due to extraordinary circumstances.

## Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Our website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Changes to this policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any material Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice in our home page and also notify you by email. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. We will strive to provide a summary of the key changes and keep prior versions in an archive for your review. If you have any other questions about this policy you may contact us at support@officedrop.com or send us a letter to 180 Fawcett St, Suite One, Cambridge, MA 02138.   
Effective Date: August 8, 2008
